In the Forecast Fragment, we want to modify the
FetchWeatherTask, so that we can pass in the
postal code parameter when we execute that task.
You can click on this class, to jump
to where it's defined or you can use this shortcut. And here you see that we
modified the generic input type, to be a
string so that the doInBackground method receives string params.
Now, we only passed in one string param,
94043. So when you see down here later, we
can read out the zeroth position in the params
array, to get that postal code. Notice that we're
using the UI builder here, and we're appending query
parameters, one by one. We define constants for these
query params, as seen here. And for the values,
we also define them up here. You can imagine
that in the future these might be configured outside
of this class, but for now we're just going
to define them here. To verify that this URI
was defined properly, we add a verbose log command
to print out the built URI. Let's verify that
the log we added actually shows up. In overflow
menu we tap Refresh. Then we see the log
tag FetchWeatherTask with our UI printed out. It says
94043, jSON format metric units, seven days. So this looks correct.